{
    "data": [
        {
            "id": 2,
            "product": {
                "productId": 2,
                "productName": "Nano Loan",
                "productCatagory": "Individual",
                "productSpecification": [
                    {
                        "name": "Loan Duration",
                        "value": "30",
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "FED",
                        "value": "16",
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "Loan Amount",
                        "value": "1000",
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "Late Payment Fee",
                        "value": "100",
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "Service Fee",
                        "value": "100",
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "Grace Period",
                        "value": "7",
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    }
                ],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "questionId": 42,
                        "question": "Number of Dependents ",
                        "questionCategory": "ADDITIONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "ENUM",
                        "answer": " 7 or more",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 28,
                        "question": "Mother's Name",
                        "questionCategory": "CNICINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "Malik",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 26,
                        "question": "Date of Birth",
                        "questionCategory": "CNICINFO",
                        "answerType": "DATE",
                        "answer": "24/12/2001",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 29,
                        "question": "Current Address",
                        "questionCategory": "PERSONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "tester",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 33,
                        "question": "Reason for Loan",
                        "questionCategory": "PERSONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "tester",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 34,
                        "question": "Employment Status",
                        "questionCategory": "INCOMEINFO",
                        "answerType": "ENUM",
                        "answer": " Own Business",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 32,
                        "question": "Marital Status",
                        "questionCategory": "PERSONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "ENUM",
                        "answer": " Widowed",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 36,
                        "question": "Industry or Sector",
                        "questionCategory": "INCOMEINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "Malik",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 44,
                        "question": "Additional Household Income, if any",
                        "questionCategory": "ADDITIONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "NUMBER",
                        "answer": "66",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 35,
                        "question": "Employer/Business Name",
                        "questionCategory": "INCOMEINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "Malik",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 22,
                        "question": "Full Name",
                        "questionCategory": "CNICINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "Malik",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 31,
                        "question": "Gender",
                        "questionCategory": "PERSONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "ENUM",
                        "answer": " Transgender",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 25,
                        "question": "CNIC Expiry Date",
                        "questionCategory": "CNICINFO",
                        "answerType": "DATE",
                        "answer": "24/12/2019",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 30,
                        "question": "City",
                        "questionCategory": "PERSONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "ENUM",
                        "answer": " Karachi",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 37,
                        "question": "Role/Designation",
                        "questionCategory": "INCOMEINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "Malik",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 40,
                        "question": "Monthly Expenses",
                        "questionCategory": "INCOMEINFO",
                        "answerType": "NUMBER",
                        "answer": "999",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 23,
                        "question": "CNIC Number",
                        "questionCategory": "CNICINFO",
                        "answerType": "NUMBER",
                        "answer": "1234567890123",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 39,
                        "question": "Monthly Salary",
                        "questionCategory": "INCOMEINFO",
                        "answerType": "NUMBER",
                        "answer": "999",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 43,
                        "question": "Residential Status",
                        "questionCategory": "ADDITIONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "ENUM",
                        "answer": " Rented",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 27,
                        "question": "City of Birth",
                        "questionCategory": "CNICINFO",
                        "answerType": "STRING",
                        "answer": "Malik",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 24,
                        "question": "CNIC Issue Date",
                        "questionCategory": "CNICINFO",
                        "answerType": "DATE",
                        "answer": "24/12/2019",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 38,
                        "question": "Total Work Experience",
                        "questionCategory": "INCOMEINFO",
                        "answerType": "ENUM",
                        "answer": " 5 - 10 Yrs",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    },
                    {
                        "questionId": 41,
                        "question": "Enter existing Loan Amount, if any",
                        "questionCategory": "ADDITIONALINFO",
                        "answerType": "NUMBER",
                        "answer": "5",
                        "expiryInDays": 0,
                        "listOfPossibleAnswers": null,
                        "mandatoryStatus": false,
                        "createdBy": null,
                        "createdAt": null,
                        "updatedBy": null,
                        "updatedAt": null
                    }
                ],
                "createdBy": null,
                "createdAt": null,
                "updatedBy": null,
                "updatedAt": null
            },
            "customer": {
                "id": 3,
                "cellNo": 3218814567,
                "fullName": null,
                "cnic": 1234567890123,
                "balance": 0,
                "pinCode": null,
                "status": null,
                "idCardFrontPath": null,
                "idCardBackPath": null,
                "idCardWithFacePath": null,
                "oneLoadStatus": false,
                "createdAt": null,
                "createdBy": null,
                "updatedAt": null,
                "updatedBy": null
            },
            "walletTypeId": 0,
            "requestedamount": 1000,
            "status": "ACCEPTED",
            "customerLoanSummary": null,
            "createdAt": "2019-12-24",
            "createdBy": null,
            "updatedAt": "2019-12-24",
            "updatedBy": null,
            "Requested_Action": false
        }
    ],
    "Requested_Action": true
}